euroffice.co.uk 2014-03-28

# What is Euroffice’s privacy policy?- Euroffice

PRIVACY POLICY

Our privacy policy is set out below. By providing personal data to us via our website at www.euroffice.co.uk (the “ **Website** ”) you consent to our processing of your data in accordance with this policy together with our terms and conditions of use. Nothing in this privacy policy shall limit your statutory rights in relation to your personal data.

Any definitions used in this Policy shall have the same meanings as provided in our terms and conditions.

 **1\. WHO WILL HOLD YOUR INFORMATION?**

> 1.1 Your information will be held by Euroffice Limited (“ **we** ”) is a company registered in England (Company No. 03877111) and our registered office is at Dome House, 48 Artillery Lane, London, E1 7LS. 
> 
> 2 If our business is sold or integrated with another business your details may be disclosed to our advisors and any prospective purchasers and their advisors and will be passed on to the new owners of the business.

**2\. THE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU WHICH WE COLLECT**  

> 2.1 The information about you which we will collect may include:
> 
> 2.1.1 Personal contact details such as name, address, contact telephone numbers and email address and any other information provided at the time of registering on our Website via the Registration Pages; 
> 
> 2.1.2 Information to assist in the operation of our services including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual;
> 
> 2.1.3 If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence;
> 
> 2.1.4 Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and fulfilment of your orders;
> 
> 2.1.5 Billing information, credit card and debit card numbers and expiration dates (“ **Payment Information.** ”)
> 
> 2.1.6 If you complete a credit [application form then we will make searches with a credit reference agency in order to determine whether or not to grant you a credit facility. We will make searches both in respect of your Company and its directors. We therefore collect the information that you submit on the credit application form and we will keep a copy of the search results from the credit reference agency.

**3\. THE INFORMATION WE HOLD ABOUT YOU**

> 3.1 We may receive information about you directly from you when you submit information to us through our Website (for example by filling in forms on the Website or indicating that you would like to join our mailing list). We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website.
> 
> 3.2 We may collect information about your computer and browsing actions by the use of Cookies (see clause 6 below).
> 
> 3.3 We may hold Payment Information however any credit card or debit card information that you provide through the Website is directly submitted to a payment server of a credit card processing bank. We do not maintain electronic or physical copies of your credit card information. 
> 
> 3.4 If you contact us by telephone or in writing, we may keep a record of that correspondence or phone call. 
> 
> 3.5 In addition, we may receive your personal information from our direct marketing activities. 
> 
> 3.6 If you complete a credit application form then we will keep a copy of that form together with copies of search results from a credit reference agency which may include information about individual directors or partners if you are a company or partnership (“ **Credit Application Information** ”).
> 
> 3.7 We may monitor or record communications with us in which you take part: 
> 
> 3.7.1 to assist us with the development of our services; 
> 
> 3.7.2 to train our staff; 
> 
> 3.7.3 if so requested by order of the Court, regulatory body or law enforcement organisation. 

**4\. PURPOSES FOR WHICH WE HOLD AND USE YOUR INFORMATION**

> 4.1 We may use your information for a number of purposes which are outlined below: 
> 
> 4.1.1 The provision of services to you:
> 
> 4.1.1.1 To administer and maintain our records;
> 
> 4.1.1.2 To ensure that our service continues to be the most appropriate service for your needs and that content from our website is presented in the most effective manner for you and your computer; 
> 
> 4.1.1.3 To verify your identity and to respond to any query that you may raise with us; and
> 
> 4.1.1.4 To fulfil any contractual obligations we have with you.
> 
> 4.1.2 We reserve the right to send all customers of our services email communications from time to time regarding updates and changes to our services and any technical, administrative and legal notices important to our website which we consider essential. 
> 
> 4.1.3 Marketing:
> 
> 4.1.3.24.1.3.1 We may use your data to provide you with information about our services or products which may be of interest to you and we may contact you about these by [post or telephone]. We will contact you by electronic means (email, SMS) only if you have consented to this. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, please adjust the settings of your membership in the “My Account” area of the website.
> 
> 4.1.3.2 We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our website users or our customers. We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target. We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.
> 
> 4.1.3.3 We may pass your personal information to carefully selected third parties for any Marketing Activities to which you consented in your Member registration and Administration registration pages. If you do not want us to use your details in this way please tick the relevant boxes on the form we use to collect your details or adjust the settings of your membership in the “[My Account”] area of the Website.
> 
> 4.1.4 Other purposes: 
> 
> 4.1.4.1 Your information may be used by us for the purpose of research and statistical analysis and internal customer service monitoring; and
> 
> 4.1.4.2 We may disclose information to its subsidiary companies or to a Court, regulatory body or law enforcement agency;
> 
> 4.1.4.3 Your Credit Application Information will be used to help us determine whether or not to grant you a credit facility with us. In addition we may use your Payment Information to determine your credit worthiness and in the process of such determination we may make such Payment Information available to banks and credit agencies.
> 
> 4.1.4.4 We will share your Payment Information with banks in order to enable transactions to be completed. 
> 
> 4.1.5 The period of use of the personal data supplied by you will not be longer than we deem necessary but may, be unlimited.   
> 

**5\. KEEPING INFORMATION UP TO DATE AND SECURE**

> 5.1 If any of the information that you have provided to us changes, for example if you change your email address or other contact details or if you wish to cancel your registration with us, please let us know the correct details by sending an email to us using this link or writing to us at the address below. 
> 
> 5.2 We are committed to protecting the security of your personal information [and Payment Information]. We have in place a level of security appropriate to the nature of the data and the harm that might result from a breach of security. However, all publicly accessible websites are susceptible to malicious practices, and we accept no liability if security is breached.

 **6\. COOKIES**

> 6.1 This website uses “ **cookies** ”. Cookies are small pieces of information which are sent by a website to your web browser and remain on your computer until they are deleted. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. For full details on Cookies including what they are, how you can prevent them being used and how Euroffice uses cookies to please [click here. ](http://www.euroffice.co.uk/helptopic.aspx?topic=146&section=42)[](http://www.euroffice.co.uk/helptopic.aspx?topic=146&section=0)
> 
> 6.2 You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site. 
> 
> 6.3 Visiting the Euroffice website with your browser settings adjusted to accept cookies tells us that you want to use our products and services and that you consent to our use of cookies and other technologies as described in our [Cookies and Privacy Policy. ](http://www.euroffice.co.uk/helpsection.aspx?section=42)[ ](http://www.euroffice.co.uk/helpsection.aspx?section=42)[ ](http://www.dev.uk/helpsection.aspx?section=42)

**7\. YOUR RIGHTS**

> 7.1 You may have certain rights under the Data Protection Act in relation to the information that we hold about you. These rights include the rights set out below: 
> 
> 7.1.1 You are entitled to have access to your personal data. You may request by writing to us (at the address given below), details of your information which we hold and the purposes for which it is held. We will provide this information within 40 days of your request, subject to any routine processing continuing between that time and the time of response. You may be charged a reasonable fee (as permitted by the Data Protection Act 1998) for this information. 
> 
> 7.1.2 You are entitled to request that we stop using information about you for the purpose of direct marketing (i.e. the communication to you (by whatever means) of any advertising or marketing material); 
> 
> 7.1.3 You are entitled to require us to ensure that no decision taken by or on behalf of us and which significantly affects you is based solely on the automated processing of your information, for the purpose of evaluating such matters as, for example, your creditworthiness, reliability or conduct; and 
> 
> 7.1.4 You are entitled to require a correction of errors in the personal information held about you. If we disagree that information is inaccurate you are entitled to apply to ask the court for an order that such erroneous information be rectified, blocked, destroyed, or erased.

 **8\. YOUR CONSENT AND CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

> By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the changes. 

**9\. CONTACT DETAILS**

> If you would like to contact us with any queries or comments regarding our privacy policy, please send an email using this link or write to: The Data Protection Officer, Euroffice Limited, Dome House, 48 Artillery Lane, London, E1 7LS.
